Finding Granny by Andrew Abel
Illustrations by Graeme Holding.
We're on a hunt for Granny.
Wherever can she be?
Grandpa's clue looks like a plant.
But it might just be a tree.
It's the plant.
The potted plant has another clue.
Let's follow it and see!
We're on a hunt for Granny.
Wherever can she be?
The clue looks like a photograph
But it might be the TV.
It's the TV!
We're on a hunt for Granny.
Wherever can she be?
The clue looks like
a comfy couch,
but which one would it be?
I think it is the orange one,
'cos it has room for three.
We're on a hunt for Granny.
Wherever can she be?
The clue looks like a pyramid,
but it might be our teepee.
It's the teepee!
We're on a hunt for Granny.
Wherever can she be?
The clue looks like a
stepping stool.
But which one would it be?
The kitchen or the bathroom one?
We'll have to go and see.
We're on a hunt for Granny.
Wherever can she be?
Surprise!
She's in the laundry room
with hugs for you and me.